awesomepennystocks.com 2010-11-19

# Privacy Policy

_**Privacy Policy**_

This policy covers how AwesomePennyStocks treats personal information that AwesomePennyStocks collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. AwesomePennyStocks, Inc. collects personal information when you register anywhere on AwesomePennyStocks. We ask for information such as your full name, full address, email address and phone number. Once you register with AwesomePennyStocks and sign in to our website, you are not anonymous to us. By becoming a member of AwesomePennyStocks, you are giving us the permission to contact you via telephone (voice broadcast/live person), text message (SMS-standard messaging rates apply-contact your carrier for details), email, direct mail and by any means necessary. AwesomePennyStocks, Inc. automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. AwesomePennyStocks, Inc. uses information for the following general purposes: to personalize the content you see, fulfill your requests, contact you, and to improve our services. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We may place a cookie on your personal computer. A cookie is a small computer file that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you make a request from our site. Cookies help us recognize you when you visit our site again. We use cookies on our site to collect session data for several purposes to personalize and improve your individual viewing experiences on our site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit. AwesomePennyStocks, Inc. may update this policy at anytime. It is up to the user to check back regularly to see if there have been changes made. The AwesomePennyStocks website requires consideration for and as a condition of allowing you access. Reading and accepting the terms of use and reading and accepting the provisions of our privacy policy are required considerations for granting you the right to visit, read or interact with it. All persons under the age of 18 are denied access to this website. If you are under 18 years of age, it is unlawful for you to visit, read, or interact with this website or its contents in any manner. This website specifically denies access to any individual that is covered by the Child Online Privacy Act (COPA) of 1998. This website reserves the right to deny access to any person or viewer for any reason. Under the terms of the privacy policy, which you accept as a condition for viewing, the website is allowed to collect and store data and information for the purpose of exclusion and for many other uses. The terms of use agreement may change from time to time. Visitors have an affirmative duty, as part of the consideration for permission to view this website, to keep themselves informed of changes. Viewers, users, or customers, collectively referred to herein as "Visitors," are parties to this agreement. The website (www.AwesomePennyStocks.com) and its owners and/or operators are parties to this agreement, herein referred to as "Website." Unless you have entered into an express written contract with this website to the contrary, visitors have no right to use this information in a commercial or public setting; they have no right to broadcast it, copy it, save it, print it, sell it, or publish any portions of the content of this website. By viewing the contents of this website you agree this condition of viewing and you acknowledge that any unauthorized use is unlawful and may subject you to civil or criminal penalties. The website and its contents are owned or licensed by the website. Material contained on the website must be presumed to be proprietary and copyrighted. Visitors have no rights whatsoever in the site content. Use of website content for any reason is unlawful unless it is done with express contract or permission of the website. The website disclaims any responsibility for the accuracy of the content of this website. Visitors assume the all risk of viewing, reading, using, or relying upon this information. Unless you have otherwise formed an express contract to the contrary with the website, you have no right to rely on any information contained herein as accurate. The website makes no such warranty. The website assumes no responsibility for damage to computers or software of the visitor or any person the visitor subsequently communicates with from corrupting code or data that is inadvertently passed to the visitor's computer. Again, visitor views and interacts with this site, or banners or pop-ups or advertising displayed thereon, at his own risk. By viewing, using, or interacting in any manner with this site, including banners, advertising, or pop-ups, and as a condition of the website to allow his lawful viewing, Visitor forever waives all right to claims of damage of any and all description based on any causal factor resulting in any possible harm, no matter how heinous or extensive, whether physical or emotional, foreseeable or unforeseeable, whether personal or business in nature. Visitor agrees as a condition of viewing, that any communication between Visitor and Website is deemed a submission. All submissions, including portions thereof, graphics contained thereon, or any of the content of the submission, shall become the exclusive property of the Website and may be used, without further permission, for commercial use without additional consideration of any kind.
